supermediastore.com 2009-04-09

# Privacy Policy

**This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store.**  
Yahoo! hosts store pages, order processing system and order data information. Yahoo! automatically collects such information but may only use this information in the aggregation. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also will automatically collect information regarding your shopping experience. Please refer to [**Yahoo! Privacy Policy**](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more detail information. 

We use third-party web beacons from Yahoo! to help analyze where visitors go and what they do while visiting our website. Yahoo! may also use anonymous information about your visits to this and other websites in order to improve its products and services and provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo!, [click here](https://reports.web.analytics.yahoo.com/optout,OptOut.vm?domain=a.analytics.yahoo.com).

* * *

**We are committed to protect your privacy online the best we can.**   
We have created our Privacy Policy ("Policy") Statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment for protecting the privacy of our shoppers. 

Questions regarding this policy should be directed to   

* * *

**What information does SuperMediaStore.com collect?**  
In order to better provide you with numerous products and services, we collect two forms of information which are about visitors: Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, more efficiency and customized time with our site.  

* * *

**Non-Personally Identifiable Information**  
This refers to information that does not, by itself, identify as a specific individual. We gather certain information about you based on where you shopped at our web site in several ways. This information is then compiled and analyzed on both personally and an aggregatly basis. Such information may include the Web site's Uniform Resource Locator ("URL") information as well as your Internet Protocol ("IP") address. A URL is the global address of documents and resources on the World Wide Web. An IP address is an identifier for computer or device on a Transmission Control Protocol/Internet Protocol ("TCP/IP") network, such as the World Wide Web. Networks use the TCP/IP protocol to route or reroute information based on the IP address of the destination. In another word, an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web, which allows web servers to locate and to identify your computer. Computer requires a IP address in order for user to communicate over the Internet.

* * *

**Shopping**  
We collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, gathering broad demographic information, enabling ads to be served on our web site, reporting Non-Personally Identifiable Information to our advertisers, and monitoring the level of activity on our site. We collect information from visitors from our site, such as the URLs they came from, their IP addresses, domain types (e.g., .com or .org), browser type, country, state, possiable telephone area code where their servers are located, the pages viewed by customers during their visits, and any search keywords entered on our site.   

* * *

**Ordering**  
When you order from us, we collect personally identifiable information from you. If you order one of our products or any services, we will collect your name, e-mail address, billing address, shipping address, telephone number, product information, payment information, order number, referring URL, IP address and a password. We collect such information in order to fill your order, and also in order to get in contact with you regarding your order and/or to send you promotional materials. Before submit your order, you will have the opportunity to review the order and make any changes in addition to the information it has already contained. Such changes might be automatically kept for future use. **We do not accept any walk-in or will call orders. All order must be shipped.**  

Security Measurement All online transactions at Yahoo! Stores are processed with 128-bit industry-standard SSL encryption held by Yahoo Store SSL Authorization Certification Encyption Key. When you enter your private information into the order form, it is transmitted across the Internet in an 128-bit high encrypted (scrambled) form, then decoded when it gets to Yahoo! Store (where your information will be kept). When viewing your data, your information is also been protected by store password, store secure key and will be encrypted until gets to us. For more security issues regarding transations please contact Yahoo! Store for more information. 

* * *

**Online Surveys and Polling**  
In order to improve our services to you, we ask some of our customers to voluntarily complete surveys, which may be collected by an independent third party. Answers from individual survey are kept confidentially although Non-Personally Identifiable Information is collected and will be disclosed to third parties. If you do not wish to participate in a survey, simply refuse such free service when you have been asked.   

* * *

**Contact Information and Third Party Data**  
If you contact Supermediastore or our customer service representatives by telephone, e-mail or letter, we may keep a record of your correspondence or comments. If you report a problem with our site, we may collect information in file which specific related to you. If you contact us through our feedback area or by calling one of our customer service representatives, we may ask for your name and e-mail address in order to send you a reply. If other users or third parties send us correspondence regarding your activities or purchases on our site, we may keep the information in a file specific related to you.   

* * *

**Surveys and Polling**  
We use a third party surveyor to run optional surveys for SuperMediaStore.com. That surveyor collects Non-Personally Identifiable Information for the sole purpose of providing reports to SuperMediaStore.com about our shoppers' interests and opinions.  

* * *

**Fulfillment**  
The information collected by SuperMediaStore.com is used only for the limited purposes of processing orders, keeping you informed about your order status, for statistical purposes, for improving our site and its performance, to serve ads, and to notify you of products or special offers that may be of interest to you. We will disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties to charge your credit card, fill your order, deliver your order, and provide customer service.. For example, we must release your credit card information to the card-issuing bank to confirm payment; and release your address and telephone information to the delivery service to deliver products that you ordered.  

* * *

**Other Parties**  
We may release account information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to enforce or apply our Terms and Conditions or to protect the rights, property, and safety of SuperMediaStore.com, our users, or others. If customers do not pay us for products ordered, we may submit their account information to a third party collection agency.   

* * *

**Services Provided on Our Site**  
Except as otherwise stated in this Policy, at present SuperMediaStore.com does not disclose its customers' Personally Identifiable Information to other merchants.   

* * *

**Compliance with Service of Process or Law Enforcement**  
Occasionally SuperMediaStore.com may be required by law enforcement or judicial authorities to provide Personally Identifiable Information to the appropriate governmental authorities. We will disclose Personally Identifiable Information upon receipt of a court order, subpoena, or to cooperate with a law enforcement investigation. SuperMediaStore.com fully cooperates with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use our services for illegal activities. We reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we in good faith believe to be unlawful.   

* * *

**What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?**  
At SuperMediaStore.com you can be assured that your personal and account information is secure, consistent with current industry standards. The importance of security for all Personally Identifiable Information associated with our customers is of utmost concern to us. Our secure servers protect the information using advanced firewall technology.  

* * *

**When you access your account information, the information is kept on a secure server.**  
All of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access by physical security means.   

* * *

**Contacting SuperMediaStore.com about privacy questions or concerns**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact SuperMediaStore.com by sending a letter to: 

Attn: Customer Service  
SuperMediaStore.com  
629 S 6th Ave.  
La Puente, CA 91746

You may also contact us by e-mail at **[](mailto:help@supermediastore.com)**
